dreambloggers.com 2014-05-24

# Privacy Policy

[Home](http://www.dreambloggers.com/)  »  Privacy Policy

##### Privacy Policy for [www.dreambloggers.com](http://www.dreambloggers.com/)

The privacy of our visitors to [www.dreambloggers.com](http://www.dreambloggers.com/) is important to us.

At [www.dreambloggers.com](http://www.dreambloggers.com/), we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit [www.dreambloggers.com](http://www.dreambloggers.com/), and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

##### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

##### Cookies and Web Sessions

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on [www.dreambloggers.com](http://www.dreambloggers.com/) to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.

##### **Email Addresses**

When you make a comment or contact us using the contact page your email id is required. Please be assured that your email address will only be used for responding to your email or comment and will never be made publicly available. We will never sell your email address to any third parties, ever.

**Comments Policy**

The author does not assume responsibility over comments he did not make on this blog. While comments are welcome from anybody, we reserve the right to remove any comment that is not deemed suitable for publication. This could include but is not limited to objection and abusive comments. Hate, racist comments, or any other form of prejudice will be removed and the poster will be banned!

Comments made for sole purpose of getting backlinks or advertizing your/any product will not be accepted. Link to third party website will require moderation and we reserve the rights to edit/delete such links.

Spam in any form will not be accepted and will be deleted immediately. We may take action against such spammers.

**Copyrights**

Supreme caution has been taken to make sure that there are no copyright infringements in terms of the multimedia content and the subject matter that is posted in this blog. If you find anything that could be considered a violation of the copyright norms, please [contact us](http://www.dreambloggers.com/contact-us/) immediately.
